[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What is it and how threatening is it going to be in the next 24 hours?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "and", "how", "threatening", "is", "it", "going", "to", "be", "in", "the", "next", "24", "hours", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "VBG", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "It is a long -term event that has to get its act together.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "long", "-term", "event", "that", "has", "to", "get", "its", "act", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What was going through my mind when I found out you want to interview me?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "going", "through", "my", "mind", "when", "I", "found", "out", "you", "want", "to", "interview", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "I'm sorry, could you say that last part again?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", ",", "could", "you", "say", "that", "last", "part", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Let me shorten my questions.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "shorten", "my", "questions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "People are calling me a hero?", "question_tokens": ["People", "are", "calling", "me", "a", "hero", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "To actually go through it, to see your family home going up in flames, to see the neighborhood where I believe your wife has lived since she was 4 years old, so many families and friends that you know being so badly affected, what does it do to a community?", "question_tokens": ["To", "actually", "go", "through", "it", ",", "to", "see", "your", "family", "home", "going", "up", "in", "flames", ",", "to", "see", "the", "neighborhood", "where", "I", "believe", "your", "wife", "has", "lived", "since", "she", "was", "4", "years", "old", ",", "so", "many", "families", "and", "friends", "that", "you", "know", "being", "so", "badly", "affected", ",", "what", "does", "it", "do", "to", "a", "community", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "It brings a community like ours very much together.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "brings", "a", "community", "like", "ours", "very", "much", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "What is your view of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Well, I think he's not a hero and I think a lot of people are trying to turn him into that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "not", "a", "hero", "and", "I", "think", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "are", "trying", "to", "turn", "him", "into", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Jeffrey, your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["Jeffrey", ",", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Can you imagine -- I mean, here is this 29-year-old high school dropout, well, he scrutinized these documents very carefully and he decided they were not a damage to national security.", "answer_tokens": ["Can", "you", "imagine", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "here", "is", "this", "29-year-old", "high", "school", "dropout", ",", "well", ",", "he", "scrutinized", "these", "documents", "very", "carefully", "and", "he", "decided", "they", "were", "not", "a", "damage", "to", "national", "security", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Should the Americans get all uptight about what the Chinese are doing to their computers if it turns out they're doing the same thing?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "the", "Americans", "get", "all", "uptight", "about", "what", "the", "Chinese", "are", "doing", "to", "their", "computers", "if", "it", "turns", "out", "they", "'re", "doing", "the", "same", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NNPS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "We have a national security agency to do foreign intelligence in other countries.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "a", "national", "security", "agency", "to", "do", "foreign", "intelligence", "in", "other", "countries", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "But when it's normal grandpa and grandpa's phone call on Mother's Day or Father's Day?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "it", "'s", "normal", "grandpa", "and", "grandpa", "'s", "phone", "call", "on", "Mother", "'s", "Day", "or", "Father", "'s", "Day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeremy Bash"]}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "TO", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ":", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Why should it be so all encompassing and why aren't the American people entitled to know about it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "it", "be", "so", "all", "encompassing", "and", "why", "are", "n't", "the", "American", "people", "entitled", "to", "know", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "DT", "VBG", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Well, because of the technology they have, they need this enormous meta data to -- as Jeremy Bash, who is a senior official said - in order to find a needle in a haystack, you need to have the haystack.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "of", "the", "technology", "they", "have", ",", "they", "need", "this", "enormous", "meta", "data", "to", "--", "as", "Jeremy", "Bash", ",", "who", "is", "a", "senior", "official", "said", "-", "in", "order", "to", "find", "a", "needle", "in", "a", "haystack", ",", "you", "need", "to", "have", "the", "haystack", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Jeffrey Toobin?", "question_tokens": ["Jeffrey", "Toobin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I think it's a terrible thought, it's a terrible idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "terrible", "thought", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "terrible", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeffrey Toobin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "He was trying quite hard to get to first base, wasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "was", "trying", "quite", "hard", "to", "get", "to", "first", "base", ",", "was", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well, he was trying to get information from journalists to prosecute people who leak.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "was", "trying", "to", "get", "information", "from", "journalists", "to", "prosecute", "people", "who", "leak", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Now, why shouldn't they also face the same potential charges as he has?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "why", "should", "n't", "they", "also", "face", "the", "same", "potential", "charges", "as", "he", "has", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Because the First Amendment specifically refers to the freedom of the press.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "the", "First", "Amendment", "specifically", "refers", "to", "the", "freedom", "of", "the", "press", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Ben Ferguson, would you jail journalists over this?", "question_tokens": ["Ben", "Ferguson", ",", "would", "you", "jail", "journalists", "over", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "No, I wouldn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Ferguson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "Isn't that what the founding fathers, Jeffrey, intended the Second Amendment to mean?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "what", "the", "founding", "fathers", ",", "Jeffrey", ",", "intended", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "to", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "This is an example how much the debate changed in this country.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "an", "example", "how", "much", "the", "debate", "changed", "in", "this", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeffrey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Did you fear that she was very seriously hurt?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "fear", "that", "she", "was", "very", "seriously", "hurt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "I wasn't afraid of the gunman, obviously, I went running back out there and he was still out there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "n't", "afraid", "of", "the", "gunman", ",", "obviously", ",", "I", "went", "running", "back", "out", "there", "and", "he", "was", "still", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "When you saw Jerri again for the first time tonight, I mean, you've obviously been through this extraordinary experience together where both of you could have lost your lives quite easily, what was that moment like for you when you -- when you met?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "saw", "Jerri", "again", "for", "the", "first", "time", "tonight", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "'ve", "obviously", "been", "through", "this", "extraordinary", "experience", "together", "where", "both", "of", "you", "could", "have", "lost", "your", "lives", "quite", "easily", ",", "what", "was", "that", "moment", "like", "for", "you", "when", "you", "--", "when", "you", "met", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "We gave each other big hugs.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "gave", "each", "other", "big", "hugs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerri"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "What is your view given what you've been through?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "given", "what", "you", "'ve", "been", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Well, Piers, I actually grew up down south.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "actually", "grew", "up", "down", "south", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Debra, say -- you want to say something?", "question_tokens": ["Debra", ",", "say", "--", "you", "want", "to", "say", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Debra wants to say one thing --", "answer_tokens": ["Debra", "wants", "to", "say", "one", "thing", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "What was your take on what happened in court today?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "take", "on", "what", "happened", "in", "court", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "Well, it was interesting because not only did he not say a word, but he walked in with his head down and he had his hands cuffed, he had his ankles cuffed as well, but I noticed in looking at the videotape later something very striking.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "interesting", "because", "not", "only", "did", "he", "not", "say", "a", "word", ",", "but", "he", "walked", "in", "with", "his", "head", "down", "and", "he", "had", "his", "hands", "cuffed", ",", "he", "had", "his", "ankles", "cuffed", "as", "well", ",", "but", "I", "noticed", "in", "looking", "at", "the", "videotape", "later", "something", "very", "striking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "Could that play a part in him avoiding the death penalty in this case which may be the only unresolved thing left?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "that", "play", "a", "part", "in", "him", "avoiding", "the", "death", "penalty", "in", "this", "case", "which", "may", "be", "the", "only", "unresolved", "thing", "left", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Well, it remains to be seen if the prosecutor or how much the prosecutor will take into account the feelings of the victims and the relatives.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "remains", "to", "be", "seen", "if", "the", "prosecutor", "or", "how", "much", "the", "prosecutor", "will", "take", "into", "account", "the", "feelings", "of", "the", "victims", "and", "the", "relatives", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Is this likely to succeed as a charge, do you think, if it comes to trial?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "likely", "to", "succeed", "as", "a", "charge", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "if", "it", "comes", "to", "trial", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Good evening, Piers, and thanks for having me on.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "evening", ",", "Piers", ",", "and", "thanks", "for", "having", "me", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "It was a happy time for me.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "happy", "time", "for", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "What did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "I first got the phone call, and I was -- I didn't believe -- not that I didn't believe it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "first", "got", "the", "phone", "call", ",", "and", "I", "was", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "believe", "--", "not", "that", "I", "did", "n't", "believe", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "PRP", ":", "CD", "NNS", "RBR", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "How did you do it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Well, first I -- 10 years later I tried to get information, and when I got the nerve to go to the precinct.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "I", "--", "10", "years", "later", "I", "tried", "to", "get", "information", ",", "and", "when", "I", "got", "the", "nerve", "to", "go", "to", "the", "precinct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "And what was the breakthrough moment?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "was", "the", "breakthrough", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "2008, I find these Background Checks.", "answer_tokens": ["2008", ",", "I", "find", "these", "Background", "Checks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "That's online service which checks people's names, right?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "online", "service", "which", "checks", "people", "'s", "names", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "And eventually you began to piece it all together and then you went to the police again?", "question_tokens": ["And", "eventually", "you", "began", "to", "piece", "it", "all", "together", "and", "then", "you", "went", "to", "the", "police", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "No, I just put that away.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "just", "put", "that", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November of 2012"]}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "So what was the moment you went to the police?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "was", "the", "moment", "you", "went", "to", "the", "police", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "November of 2012.", "answer_tokens": ["November", "of", "2012", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "And how quickly was it the police found the guy?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "quickly", "was", "it", "the", "police", "found", "the", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Very quickly.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "quickly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130612pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "But all from the information you gave them?", "question_tokens": ["But", "all", "from", "the", "information", "you", "gave", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "I guess.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]